<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Psycasts Expanded - Puppeteer</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, Taranchuk, Reann Shepard</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modVersion>1.0.2</modVersion>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</packageId>
			<displayName>Royalty</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VPsycastsE</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Psycasts Expanded</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2842502659</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VPE.Puppeteer</packageId>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VPsycastsE</li>
		<li>vanillaexpanded.achievements</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>Vanilla Psycasts Expanded - Puppeteer introduces a brand new, rare psycaster path available only to those who studied the secret arts in their childhood - notably, high imperial nobles. Puppeteer is a path focused on providing the master of puppets with mindless servants that he or she directly controls. It allows the puppeteer to move their consciousness and personality to a random puppet, essentially allowing for a wicked sort of immortality.
Puppeteers are able to subdue their prisoners with a twisted psychic abomination called the brain leech, which will lay the foundations of a brand new puppet. Such brain leech can then seize control of the prisoner if the puppetmaster sends out a puppeting signal. Puppets care not for recreation, joy or comfort, and exist only to serve the puppet master. Any experience they gained is shared with their overlord, and if they are chosen, they may be ascended - their existence fizzles out in a blaze of utter destruction, while anything that they were becomes food for the evil psycaster that puppeted them.
As stated before, this Psycaster path is only available to those of Imperial backstory, similar to the Archotechist. Your colonists may, however, become puppeteers if they gain a puppeteer neurotrainer.
</description>
</ModMetaData>